ptrack1.com 2015-10-07

# 

* Overview

This document establishes the privacy policies of Your-Surveys.com as well as its compliance with specific national and international jurisdictions (including the privacy regulations and laws thereof). The publication of this document rescinds all previous privacy policies – implied, spoken or written – and establishes 

* Organization Information 

The principal activities of Your-Surveys.com are market research. 

Modern information and communication technologies play a fundamental role in the activities of Your-Surveys.com.

Your_Surveys.com is based in United States and at the following postal address:   
3625 Brookside Parkway, # 300  
Alpharetta, GA, 30022  
United States of America  
Your Surveys can be reached via e-mail at info@your-surveys.com 

* Anonymous Access

Visitors can access the website/application home pages and browse sites/applications without disclosing personal data. 

* Services and Links 

Your-Surveys.com sites and applications may include links to third-party web/mobile service providers. Your-Surveys.com is not responsible for the content, accuracy, or privacy policies of third-party web/mobile services. 

* Automatic Data Collection 

Your_surveys.com may collect information from your computer, mobile phone or other access device. The information sent to us includes, but is not limited to, data on the pages you access, your computer IP address, referral data, device identifiers, the type of operating system you’re using, your location (GPS), mobile network information, standard web log data and other information. Web log data includes the browser type you’re using and traffic to and from our site to determine trends, administer the site, track user movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. 

* Data Collection and Purpose 

Your Surveys respects your privacy and will never sell, rent, lease or otherwise provide your information (name, address, email etc.) to any third party. 

Your Surveys will not contact you through email or mail for any purpose. 

Additionally, we may share personal data and demographic information we collect from you with our clients or partners in connection with market research surveys opportunities, offered by our clients or partners for several purposes, including, without limitation, facilitating your participation in a survey(s), offers, fraud detection and prevention, copyright infringement, data validation, incentive or reward fulfillment (if applicable), identifying respondents for re-contact surveys and offers, or communications, database matching, data append, coding, data segmentation, and/or developing data insights regarding survey and offer participants. 

We reserve the right to share your identity with others within the stipulations of data protection in an attempt to prevent further fraudulent activity. We may also obtain information about you from third parties such as identity verification services 

Access to collected personal data is available upon request. 

* Sharing and Cookies

Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually configure your browser to prevent this occurrence. Not accepting cookies may make certain features of Your-Surveys.com unavailable to you; though we will make every effort to ensure that users who have disabled cookies are denied access only to those portions of the website that legitimately require cookies for their functionality. To opt-out of these cookies and for more information, please visit aboutads.info/choices and/or networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp. 

Your-Surveys assists clients and/or partners in recruiting for their online/mobile ad exposure programs. In connection with a client’s and/or partner’s online/mobile ad exposure program, you can participate in market research surveys regarding specific online ads and promotions that our client or partner is testing for its client. To facilitate the completion of these offers and surveys, we and/or our client/partner may write, set or read first and third party cookies, locally shared/stored objects, flash cookies, and/or any other related technology (each a “Cookie Technology” and collectively the “Cookie Technologies”). The Cookie Technologies may be written, set or read in various locations, including and without limitation, on our and/or our client/partner’s website(s), system(s), or server(s). If you participate, a unique identification number and a source identification number may be stored in the Cookie Technology, to allow you to be re-contacted about the online ad or promotion and to determine whether you have seen, clicked on or otherwise interacted with the online ad or promotion. If you have interacted with the online ad or promotion, our client or partner will send us your unique identification number and a link to the specific survey or offer on the online ad or promotion and you will receive an email invitation to participate in and complete the survey once opt-in for email. Survey participation is completely voluntary and you can opt-out at any time. If you do not wish to participate in the Online Ad Exposure Program, please visit [http://www.nielsen-online.com/corp.jsp?section=leg_prs&nav=1](http://www.nielsen-online.com/corp.jsp?section=leg_prs&nav=1) and <http://www.safecount.net/viewyourcookiesinformation_optinout.php>. 

* Children's Privacy 

Your-Surveys.com does not knowingly collect personal data from individuals under the age of 13. Minors 13 to 18 are permitted to access the services of the site only with parental permission. It is the responsibility of the individual and the parent to ensure such permissions are obtained. It is possible that by fraud or deception we may receive information given to us or pertaining to children under 13. If we are notified of this and as soon as we verify the information, we will immediately delete the information from our servers. 

* Disclosure 

Except as set forth herein, Your-Surveys.com does not disclose personal data to subsidiaries or other organizations without your permission or where it can reasonably be inferred from the circumstances that you consent to the disclosure to the third parties. Your-Surveys.com tries to limit the information it provides to third parties to the information they need to help Your-Surveys.com provide goods and services to you. 

* Third Party Advertisements 

The Your-Surveys.com websites, mobile applications and emails contain links to various other sites that are not owned by us. While Your-Surveys.com makes every effort to ensure that our advertisers post clear and complete Privacy Policies and observe appropriate data practices, each of these sites/applications has a privacy policy that may differ from that of Your-Surveys.com. The privacy practices of other websites/applications and companies are not covered by this policy. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites/applications. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site/application and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collect personally identifiable information. 

Your-Surveys.com may share non-personally identifiable information collected via the service in aggregate, anonymous form with advertisers or other third parties so that they may better evaluate what products and services are most appealing to different segments of the user base. Your-Surveys.com does not disclose your first name/last name, address, email address or any other Personal Information to these third parties unless you give your express consent. 

* Confidentiality and Security 

Your-Surveys.com does not employ the use of secure transmission methods to send personal data. 

Your-Surveys.com has implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data from unauthorized access, improper use or disclosure, unauthorized modification and unlawful destruction or accidental loss. 

Your-Surveys.com employees and data processors with access or association to the processing of personal data are obliged to respect the confidentiality of visitor personal data. 

Your-Surveys.com does not disclose personal data to State institutions and authorities unless required by law. 

* Access to Personal Data

Visitors may request access to their own specific personal information collected by Your-Surveys.com by sending an email to info@your-surveys.com 

Access to personal information may require proof of identity. Access to personal data is provided without charge. Personal data may be challenged or updated and, where appropriate, data will be completed, erased, rectified or amended. Your-Surveys.com reserves the right to refuse access to personal data. In such a case, reasons will be given for refusal. 

You can close your account through our website. If you close your account, we will mark your account in our database as "Closed," but will keep your account information in our database. This is necessary to deter fraud or abuse of the site, by ensuring that persons who try to commit fraud or abuse of the site will not be able to avoid detection simply by closing their account and opening a new account. However, if you close your account, your personally-identifiable information will not be used by us for any further purposes, nor sold to or shared with third parties, except as necessary to prevent fraud and assist law enforcement or as required by law.

* Privacy Compliance

The Your-Surveys.com privacy policy is compliant with the following international and national regulations:   
Global: OECD Privacy Guidelines on the Protection of Privacy and Transborder Flows of Personal Data Guidelines   
Global: United Nations Guidelines for the Regulation of Personal Data Files Adopted by General Assembly Resolution 45/95 of 14 December 1990   
United States: Privacy Act of 1974   
European Union: European Convention on Human Rights   
Canada: Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act   
Privacy compliance is ensured by periodic self-assessment.  

* Privacy Support 

Enquiries or concerns about the Your-Surveys.co m privacy policy can be directed to: Mathijs de Jong, CEO  
3625 brookside parkway, ste 300  
Alpharetta, GA, 30022  
United States of America  
E-mail: info@your-surveys.com
